const data = [
  {
    question:
      " Who is the only one of the following South Africans not to have won the Nobel Peace prize?",
    incorrectAnswers: ["F. W. de Klerk", "Desmond Tutu", "Nelson Mandela"],
    correctAnswer: "Steve Biko",
  },
  {
    question: " Of which church was Desmond Tutu an important leader?",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Roman Catholic ", "Methodist ", "Baptist"],
    correctAnswer: "Anglican",
  },
  {
    question:
      " The so called #FeesMustFall Protest began in October 2015 to protest an increase in the price of what?",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Water", "Property taxes ", "Oil"],
    correctAnswer: "College tuition",
  },

  {
    question:
      " March 21 is celebrated as Human Rights Day in South Africa to commemorate the 1960 massacre of black South Africans and to prevent something like it from ever happening again. Where did this massacre take place?",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Alexandar", "Soweto ", "Johannesburg"],
    correctAnswer: "Sharpeville",
  },

  {
    question:
      " Which of the following parties did not contest the 1994 general elections?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "Soccer Party",
      "National Party ",
      "Pan Africanist Congress ",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Azanian People's Organisation",
  },

  {
    question: " Who was Buthelezi?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "Nelson Mandela's cousin",
      "The President of Zambia in 1996",
      "The leader of the South African Parliament in 1996",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "The leader of the Inkatha Freedom Party ",
  },

  {
    question:
      "  April 27 marks the anniversary of the election of Nelson Mandela as president of South Africa, and is celebrated as a national holiday. What is the name of this holiday?",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Worker's day", "Human-Rights day", "Mandela day"],
    correctAnswer: "Freedom Day",
  },

  {
    question: "  Where is the South African Parliament located?",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Johannesburg", "Pretoria", "Bloemfotein"],
    correctAnswer: "Cape Town",
  },

  {
    question:
      " Which famous world icon, who is best known for his work outside of South Africa, came to Johannesburg in 1902 and led a nonviolent movement in 1913?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "Frederick Douglass",
      "Martin Luther King Jr.",
      "Liu Xiaobo",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Mohandas Gandhi",
  },
  {
    question:
      " Which famous world icon, who is best known for his work outside of South Africa, came to Johannesburg in 1902 and led a nonviolent movement in 1913?",
    incorrectAnswers: ["31 May 1966", "31 May 1960", "31 May 1962"],
    correctAnswer: "31 May 1961",
  },
  {
    question:
      " June 26, 2005 marked the fiftieth anniversary of the signing of this ANC document, which laid the foundation of the ANC's policy for decades.",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "The ANC's Constitution",
      "Morogoro Declaration",
      "Three Doctors' Pact",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Freedom Charter",
  },
  {
    question:
      " Which of the following has never been an African National Congress president?",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Oliver Tambo ", "Thabo Mbeki", "Nelson Mandela "],
    correctAnswer: "Chris Hani",
  },
];

export default data;
